import { title } from "process";

export const options = [
    {
        label: "How does this work",
        slug: "how-does-this-work",
        questions: [
            {
                "question": "What's it all about?",
                "answer": "Sellzey is a service that buys brand new, factory-sealed, authentic products in bulk, mainly from categories like electronics, home improvement goods, and tools. It offers customers an easy way to sell their unwanted items without the hassle and risks associated with auctions or third-party platform fees and returns."
            },
            {
                "question": "Why Should I trust Sellzey?",
                "answer": "At Sellzey, providing a phenomenal customer experience and building trust with our customers is our top priority. We understand the importance of the trust our customers place in us and continuously strive to deliver securely and in a timely manner. Our specialized team ensures the authenticity of products, and we honor our promise to provide top dollar for your goods."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does Sellzey accept items from outside of the United States?",
                "answer": "No, at present, Sellzey only accepts shipments from within the United States."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is there a limit on the number of items I can sell?",
                "answer": "No, there is no limit. You can sell as many items as you want. However, all bulk sales are subject to final approval and may be canceled for any reason deemed necessary."
            },
            {
                "question": "What if my products delivered are not authentic?",
                "answer": "Our specialized team validates the authenticity of products. If any products have a 'red flag' during the Quality Assessment process, we will be unable to pay for them, and all products will be returned to you."
            },
            {
                "question": "Why should I sign up for an account?",
                "answer": "Signing up allows you to track your offers and have your information saved with us for faster checkout in the future."
            },
            {
                "question": "I haven't received a Confirmation Email. What should I do?",
                "answer": "Please ensure that you have entered a valid email address and check your Junk or Spam Mail Folder. Some email programs may mistakenly misroute your confirmation email. We recommend adding Sellzey to your list of Safe Senders to ensure proper email delivery."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        label: "Payouts",
        slug: "payouts",
        questions: [
            {
                "question": "How and when will I get paid?",
                "answer": "Your payment will be sent after we receive and inspect your item(s), typically taking 1 to 2 business days. Payment is processed within 24 hours of approval. Expedited processing is available for 1 business day."
            },
            {
                "question": "What should I do if I haven't received my payment?",
                "answer": "Once we've inspected your item(s), we typically issue payment within 24 hours. You'll receive an email notification for each payment. Time to receive payment varies based on your chosen method."
            },
            {
                "question": "What payment methods do you offer?",
                "answer": "We currently offer PayPal. As your reputation grows, zelle/venmo/cashapp will be enabled for your profile."
            },
            {
                "question": "Can I change my payment method?",
                "answer": "Contact us via email to change your payment method. Changes will reflect in the 'Remarks' notes on your offer page."
            },
            {
                "question": "What if I provided wrong personal information or selected the wrong payment type?",
                "answer": "For incorrect payment type, contact us via email for changes. Changes will reflect in the 'Adjustment' notes on your offer page. Wrong personal information can't be modified for submitted offers due to security reasons."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        label: "Shipping",
        slug: "shipping",
        questions: [
            {
                "question": "How long do I have to ship my item to you?",
                "answer": "The price quoted by Sellzey is valid for ten (10) days. If we receive your item AFTER ten (10) days, Sellzey shall re-evaluate your item and price it at the CURRENT market value."
            },
            {
                "question": "What if my item is damaged in shipping?",
                "answer": "It is your responsibility to ensure that your item(s) are fully secure when you ship them. If the box is secure and does not appear damaged, but the item inside was not secure and got damaged, we will return the damaged products to your address at no cost."
            },
            {
                "question": "How do I ship items to Sellzey?",
                "answer": "Once your offer is approved, you'll have to print the offer packing slip, place it inside the package, and carefully package the box. We prefer shipments through UPS or FedEx. Once your package is ready, drop it off at the nearest FedEx or UPS location. After shipping, update tracking information on your offer page for us to process funds upon validation."
            }
        ]

    }
]